上周《这视频有毒：名人大糗事》可真是大丰收哇
Well it's been a big week for Viral Video: Celeb Meltdowns
听译：Shiny
本字幕作品由MattBomer字幕园制作 禁止二传二改 请勿用于商业用途 由此产生的法律责任与字幕组及相关制作者无关  @MattBomerChina
首先  有Chloe Grace Moretz怒斥“Downloader”里的新人Brian Butler
First there was Chloe Grace Moretz reaming out newcomer Brian Butler from the Downloader
校对：_放^
然后我们的好哥们儿Kevin Donnelly在红毯上被大名鼎鼎的Kristen Bell狠狠地整了一发
and then our good buddy Kevin Donnelly got the business from the non-other than Kristen Bell on the red carpet of The Boss
后期：森林
啊  这特么还真有点过分
Ooh that was nasty
很多人都说这大概是(Kevin)传奇生涯的终结
A lot of people say this could be the end for the legendary correspondentce
我们今天邀请到了Kevin来把这整个事件澄清一下
We invited Kevin over this morning to set the record straight
他现在来了吗
Is he here with us?
呃...在这
Uhh yeah
他出现了吗
Did he show up
Ryan Seacrest!
Seacrest,Ryan
Seacrest  见到你真高兴啊哥们儿
Seacrest! Good to see you man!
快过来  伐开心  要抱抱
Come here, gimme some love
我们是好哥们儿对不对   - 啊不  算了吧算了吧
We're brothers  -I'm good, I'm good
看看这小白内内  快坐下来吧
Look at those tighty whiteys, have a seat
你知道么  最搞笑的是  我当时在那里
This is funny, I was there
啊好好好  你倒是先坐下来啊
Oh yes, could you please sit on the chair though?
我累炸了
I'm so tired
好的知道了但是你能不能先坐下来
OK but can you please sit on the chair?
我一整夜都没睡
I've been up all night
你这床太不舒服了啊
Your bed is so uncomfortable
各位同志们！重大消息！
Hey guys look at me
我嘞个去Britney  我以前从来没见过你跑
Jesus Britney, I've never seen you run before
发生了啥
What happened?
Kevin被炒啦
Kevin got FIRED
这真是太------------难过了
That is so super sad for him
他还好吗
Is he OK?
我不觉得诶
I don't think so
今天早上六点的时候  他发推说“NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO----"
This morning, at 6 am, he tweeted: "NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO-----"
好的懂了  好多个“O”对吧
We got it, a lot of "O"s
这可不好
This is not good
你造么  我开始有点为他难过了
You know what, I'm starting to feel bad for the guy
我是说  他们大概今天就要把他换下去了
I mean, they're probably gonna replace him today
我得走了...就现在  我还有个会要开
I've gotta go like right now, I have a meeting
我今天来大姨妈了...我得给我经纪人打个电话
I've just started my period so I've gotta call my agents
你们是这世界上最糟糕的人了  你们知道的对吧
You're both the worst humans ever, you know that right
Deckard  你也这德行
Deckard, you too?
我也有做梦的权利好伐
I have dreams
我在这小破镇子上称霸了28年
I'm the one who's dominated this whole friggin town for 28 years
然而我现在竟然他妈的坐在车里吃奇多  脑子他妈的糊成一坨
And now I'm in my car eating Cheetos cause I can't fucking get my head straight
不好意思我现在真的显得非常的无理
I'm sorry I'm being so rude right now
不不不  没关系
No it's OK
好的  那么  这电影拍起来好玩吗
OK so like...was this movie fun to make?
啊是的  非常好玩  我们...
Yeah it was really fun, we had a great...
天啦撸这真是太棒了  天哪你太好玩了
OMG this is so great, omg you'are so interesting
这就是为什么我喜欢这个角色   George Hardy
That's why I love this character, George Hardy
他不仅仅是个法官  你懂的  他是...
He's more than just a judge, you know, he's...
好好  等一下
Yes, yes, just a sec
看来是有好消息啊
Got some good news (- Hello)
没事没事  一点都不忙
Yeah no no no,not busy at all
然后...你浴袍下面穿着啥
And so, what are you wearing under the robe?
我在问你问题
I'm asking you a question
我觉得你应该...你应该把电话放下
You should probably...you should probably put that down
臣妾做不到哇
I can't, I wish I could, I wish I could
我的妈呀  这特么就很有点尴尬了
Oh my god this is really awkward
非常抱歉
I'm so sorry
我的公关呢
Where's my publicist?
好的我这就来  不好意思
Yeah I'm coming right now, I'm so sorry
好的好的  我马上来
Yeah yeah, I'll be there
已经在路上了  马上到
On our way, just a second
我们是被袭击了嘛还是怎么的
Are we under attack or something?
我才是那个该坐在里面采访Matt Bomer的人
I should be in there talking to Matt Bomer
我的霜糖呢
Where's the frosting?
哦哦这儿啊
There we go
我知道你在电话上忙什么
I know what you're on your phone about
我已经看出来了
I've figured it out
是关于Kevin Donnelly的工作那事儿是吧
It's the Kevin Donnelly job thing
啊不是的  只是在看视频而已
Oh no I'm just watching this video
就是他们给熊猫背上装了个纸飞机
It's got a panda with a little paper jet pack on it
我要看
Let me see
你看这个 看这个
Wait watch that, watch that
我滴妈
OMG
天哪太可爱了
Omg so cute
这个好棒啊我的天
That's good man
太可爱了
So cute
把刚才那个重放一次
Do that again
嘿  能不能帮我保守个秘密
Hey can you keep a secret
我刚跟我的代理通完电话
I just got off the phone with my reps
显然的  Kevin这个职位的候选范围已经缩小到我和另外一个人了
Apparently it's down to me and one other person for Kevin's job at the fix
所以我能拿到这份工作的
So I could get the job
然后我赶紧开心地喝了我的绿果汁  红果汁和米色果汁压压惊
and then I lounge my line of green juices, and then my red juices and then my beige juices
我一直没机会跟你说
I never had the chance to tell you
但是我真的很欣赏你还有你的工作
But I really admire you and your work and...
真是太谢谢你了
Thank you so much, that is so nice
你知道的我从来对你没有什么意见的
You know I never actually had an opinion about you
但是听完你刚才那一番甜言蜜语之后  我挺喜欢你的
But after you said that nice thing about me, I like you
呃..谢谢你
Thank you?
对  我再也不要回到那里面去了
Yeah I'm not going back in there
这些人简直他妈的都是疯子
These people are fucking crazy
让车在侧门接我吧...我的天啊
Just have the car pick me up on the side entrance OK?...oh Jesus
我一会儿给你回电话
I'm calling you back
Kevin你好呀
Hey there Kevin
哈喽  哎哟我去  你看上去一副早餐吃的玉米片里被人拉了翔的样子
Hey, wow you look like someone's shit in your cornflakes this morning, man
你还好吗
Are you OK?
就...能不能让我一个人待会儿
Just..just can you leave me alone OK?
来
Ok
给我来点奇多
Give me the Cheetos
如果你是准备给我来个慰问或者打打气什么的
If you're here to give me,like, a pep talk or trying to cheer me up or anything like that
省省吧  没用的
It's not gonna work
绝对不是来安慰你的  我只是要来跟你讲个故事
It's not a pep talk, I just wanna tell you a story
我出生在密苏里州的圣路易斯
I was born in St.Louis, Missouri
自打我记事起
And ever since I can remember,
我唯一想做的是  就是参与到这些故事讲述的过程之中
all I wanted to do was to be a part of the story-telling process
它改变了我的人生
It changed my life
所以我去了纽约  然后我说“不，爸爸，这是我的梦想”
So I went to NY, and I Said "No dad, these are my dreams"
我得在一个叫做“黑凤凰粉凤凰粉红凤凰灰凤凰”的广告公司当话务员
I had to answer phones at an advertising agency called "Messner Vetere Berger Schmetterer"
你能念出那个名字吗
Can you say that?
我念不出来
I can't say that
我也不行
Neither could I
后来我发现  我有把好嗓子哇
I found out that I had a voice you know
我有一只小毛驴我从来也不骑
Yankee doodle went to town, riding on a pony
（歌词）
Camptown races sing~ Come on~ All the doo-dah day
Oh Danny Boy, oh Danny Boy, I love you so
真的好棒
It's really great
这就让我意识到《麻辣法官》为什么老少咸宜
Yeah that's when I realized that Judge Hottie is perfect for the whole family
不过...我没看出来这跟我有什么相关
I don't know how that's really relevant to me tho
哦不是  跟你无关
Oh it's not, it's not relevant to you
我今天对着你的那些...自我陶醉的蠢货同事们没机会讲讲我自己的经历
I never got a chance to talk about myself with all your...self involved pricks
他们只顾着看着手机  然后跑来跑去
on your cell phones and running out
因为我是那个灾难的主人公  就在这儿
Cause I'm the one that's kinda having a crisis, right here
我的天哪  对不起
OMG I'm so sorry
我才是那个坐在车里  撸瑟一样吃着奇多的人
I'm the one in my car, eating Cheetos
天哪真的是太对不起了
I'm so sorry man
我今天的状态也是一团糟
I'm in junkie mode today
我...不好意思我一直在自说自话
I'm like just...uhh god I'm all about my narrative
你...这其实很简单的
You...This is easy man
你得停下做这么个辣鸡的人
You need to stop being a garbage human being
你有女票吗  还是男票
You have a girl? You have a guy?
我曾经有个女票  她就在里面
I had a girl and she's in there
而且她想踹了我
and she's trying to leave me
是男人就去把她追回来啊
So go get her tiger
但是首先你得洗洗澡
But you should shower first
你闻起来像坨屎
You smell like shit
我有吗
Do I?
闻起来真的那样吗
Do I smell like that?
真的  字面意思上的屎  超恶心
Literal, shit, it's bad
我都能闻到便便的味道了
I can smell like poop
一整车都是
It's permitting the whole car
我还没进车里的时候都闻到了
I smell that before I even got here
Britney!
我的天哪Kevin
Omg Kevin
跟你港  Matt Bomer刚才教我重新做人了
Listen, Matt Bomer just told me the meaning of life
请回心转意吧
Please take me back
原谅我所做的一切
Please forgive me for everything
我保证我再也不辜负你了
I promise I won't disappoint you
让我想想...
Let me think about it
当！然！不！
FUCK NO
诶  是你的手机吗
Is that you?
哈喽  这里是Brian
Hello this is Brian
对  啊啥
Yes..What?
呃...当然  非常感谢
Uhhh of course, thank you so much
电话谁打来的
Who was that phone call from?
呃...我刚拿到了Kevin的那个职位了
I...just got the job at the fix
什么鬼  一定是在逗我
What? Wait there's gotta be some kind of mistake
就是在逗你
It is like a mistake I think
呵呵  万恶的男权社会啊
The god damn patriarchy
我真为你高兴啊
I'm so happy for you
好好享受你的采访8分钟吧
Hey, enjoy your 8 minutes
嘿Kev  他们让你回来啦
Heyy Kev, they let you back
诶等会  好吧  嗨
Oh wow, OK, hi
你给我听着
Umm listen,
知道刚才怎么了嘛   -我们还在拍吗
Guess what just didn't go well  -Are we rolling?
什么  怎么啦
What, what's that?
我  回到这里  试着  你懂得  像你说的那样硬气起来什么的
Me, coming back in here and trying to, you know, being the tiger and everything
真他妈谢谢你这日狗的建议啊
Thank you for the shitty fucking advice
喂喂  你等会
Wow, wow, buddy
你知道么  我以为之前我的职业生涯算是日了狗了
You know what, my career, I thought it was fucked before
现在这算是日了苍狼了
Now it's just super fucked
我只是试图让你冷静下来啊哥们儿  -你有体会过这种被日翻天的感觉吗
I was just trying to calm down you from the heart man  -Have you ever been super fucked？
我刚才就经历过了这种被日炸天的感觉
I just got super fucked
而且  就是他妈的因为你这个蠢出翔的建议
And you know what, it was because you're shitty stupid fucking...
喂  手放干净点儿  -你他妈给我站起来
Now take it easy with that finger  -No stand the fuck up
手给我放干净点儿  -他妈的把这玩儿给我挪开
You take it easy with that finger  -Get the fucking thing away from me
站起来啊你
Stand up
我现在要出去了
I'm gonna go outside,
我会等在我车旁边  你最好给我滚出来
I'm gonna be by on my car, and you're gonna come out there
我要让你看看什么叫被日翻的感觉  -这就来啊  亲爱的哥们儿
And I'm gonna show you what is it like to be super fucked  -I will be right after my dear friend
你刚才有在拍吗
Were you rolling?